Scenic Hudson, Inc. Administrative History Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 8; 3.67 linear feet Boxes: 52 - 63 Folders: 610 - 763
  - Hyde Park Waterfront Program, Schedules&Research (Folder 682, Box 57)
  - Hyde Park Waterfront Program, Contracts (Folder 683, Box 57)
  - Idlewood Brook Development, Legal Materials (Folder 684, Box 57)
  - Idlewood Brook Development, Clippings (Folder 685, Box 57)
  - Idlewood Brook Development, Correspondence (Folder 686, Box 57)
  - Idlewood Brook Development, Maps&Sketches (Folder 687, Box 57)
  - Idlewood Brook Development, Miscellaneous (Folder 688, Box 57)
  - Indian Point, Printed Material (Folder 689, Box 57)
  - Indian Point, Clippings&Press Releases (Folder 690, Box 57)
  - Inform (Folder 691, Box 57)
  - Kingston Arms Project, Correspondence (Folder 692, Box 57)
  - Kingston Arms Project, Clippings&Printed Material (Folder 693, Box 57)
  - Kinkle Property (Folder 694, Box 57)
  - Larson Report, Printed Material (Folder 695, Box 58)
  - Larson Report, Correspondence (Folder 696, Box 58)
  - Larson Report, Clippings (Folder 697, Box 58)
  - Metz Property, Correspondence (Folder 698, Box 58)
  - Metz Property, Draft Statement (Folder 699, Box 58)
  - Metz Property, Draft Appendix A (Folder 700, Box 58)
  - Metz Property, Draft Appendix B&C (Folder 701, Box 58)
  - Niagara Mohawk Power Corp. (Folder 702, Box 58)
  - Octagon House, Carl Carmer (Folder 703, Box 59)
  - Osborn Castle, Correspondence (Folder 704, Box 59)
  - Osborn Castle, Printed Material&Minutes (Folder 705, Box 59)
  - Osborn Castle, Clippings&Photographs (Folder 706, Box 59)
  - Osborn Castle, Legal Papers (Folder 707, Box 59)
  - (Box 59)
  - Palisades Interstate Park, Commission Correspondence (Folder 708, Box 60)
  - Palisades Interstate Park, Clippings&Printed Material (Folder 709, Box 60)
  - Parks, Newsletters (Folder 710, Box 60)
  - Parks, Correspondence (Folder 711, Box 60)
  - Parks, Clippings (Folder 712, Box 60)
  - Philipstown, Correspondence&Notes (Folder 713, Box 60)
  - Philipstown, Microwave Towers (Folder 714, Box 60)
  - Plum Point (Folder 715, Box 60)
  - Putnam County Historical Society, Letters&Briefs to FPC 1964-1970 (Folder 716, Box 60)
  - Putnam County Historical Society, Files to Jean Saunders (a) (Folder 717, Box 60)
  - Putnam County Historical Society, Files to Jean Saunders (b) (Folder 718, Box 60)
  - Putnam County Historical Society, Files to Jean Saunders (c) (Folder 719, Box 60)
  - Putnam County Historical Society, Files to Jean Saunders (d) (Folder 720, Box 60)
  - Putnam County Historical Society, Miscellaneous Documents (Folder 721, Box 60)
  - Rod Vandivert, Correspondence (Folder 722, Box 61)
  - Rod Vandivert, Biography (Folder 723, Box 61)
  - Rod Vandivert, Reports&Speeches (Folder 724, Box 61)
  - Rod Vandivert, Statements (Folder 725, Box 61)
  - Rod Vandivert, Corps of Engineers Statements (Folder 726, Box 61)
  - Scenic Easements&Historic Preservation (Folder 727, Box 61)
  - South Queensbury Industrial Interceptor, Hudson River Outfall (Folder 728, Box 61)
  - Stonihurst on Hudson (Folder 729, Box 61)
  - Taskforce (Folder 730, Box 61)
  - Ulsterites Fight Over Flight Noise, Background (Folder 731, Box 61)
  - Ulsterites Fight Over Flight Noise, Correspondence (Folder 732, Box 61)
  - Ulsterites Fight Over Flight Noise, News& Reports (Folder 733, Box 61)
  - Alsen Coal, Clippings&Correspondence (Folder 734, Box 62)
  - American Legacy @ MASC, General (Folder 735, Box 62)
  - 1974 Annual Meeting (Folder 736, Box 62)
  - The 1977 Blackout, News Clippings (Folder 737, Box 62)
  - Clermont Rodeo&Ranch, Clippings&News (Folder 738, Box 62)
  - Editorials (Folder 739, Box 62)
  - April 1973 Energy Discussion, General Information (Folder 740, Box 62)
  - Governor Rockefeller, Statements (Folder 741, Box 62)
  - Governor Rockefeller, Correspondence 1964-1965 (Folder 742, Box 62)
  - Greenway Council, Clippings (Folder 743, Box 62)
  - Harpers Magazine, Civil Engineering Correspondence (Folder 744, Box 62)
  - Hudson Highlands, West Point Correspondence (Folder 745, Box 62)
  - Hudson Flood Skimming Project, Legal Material (Folder 746, Box 62)
  - Hudson Flood Skimming Project, Clippings (Folder 747, Box 62)
  - Hudson Study Report (Folder 748, Box 62)
  - Hyde Park Waterfront Project (Folder 749, Box 62)
  - Land Purchases (Folder 750, Box 62)
  - Land Transactions (Folder 751, Box 62)
  - National Historic Preservations (Folder 752, Box 62)
  - News Ads (Folder 753, Box 62)
  - News Letters (Folder 754, Box 62)
  - Parks, Printed Material (Folder 755, Box 63)
  - PASNY (Folder 756, Box 63)
  - Philipstown, Clippings (Folder 757, Box 63)
  - Quarry Agreements (Folder 578, Box 63)
  - Richard Ottinger (Folder 759, Box 63)
  - Richard Ottinger, Press Releases (Folder 760, Box 63)
  - Scenic Riverway, Correspondence (Folder 761, Box 63)
  - Scenic Riverway, Statements&Hearings (Folder 762, Box 63)
  - Speeches (Folder 763, Box 63)
- Adjudicatory Hearings, 9; 2 linear feet Boxes: 64 - 67 Folders: 764 - 795
  Legal briefs and court documents relating to various environmental issues inthe Hudson Valley.
  - General Correspondence (Folder 764, Box 64)
  - GE Correspondence (Folder 765, Box 64)
  - New York Farm Bureau (Folder 766, Box 64)
  - Dept of Environmental Conservation (Folder 767, Box 64)
  - Hudson Falls Chamber of Commerce (Folder 768, Box 64)
  - PCB Hearing Notes (Folder 769, Box 64)
  - Reg. Review Group (Folder 770, Box 64)
  - Public Participation (Folder 771, Box 64)
  - Final Brief, Transcript Request (Folder 772, Box 65)
  - Legal Briefs (a) (Folder 773, Box 65)
  - Legal Briefs (b) (Folder 774, Box 65)
  - Legal Briefs (c) (Folder 775, Box 65)
  - Legal Briefs (d) (Folder 776, Box 65)
  - GE Testimony (Folder 777, Box 66)
  - Testimony (Folder 778, Box 66)
  - Testimony - other parties (Folder 779, Box 66)
  - Application for Approval (Folder 780, Box 66)
  - Exhibits (Folder 781, Box 66)
  - Memorandum of Law (Folder 782, Box 66)
  - ALJ Memorandum (Folder 783, Box 66)
  - Petitions Notice (Folder 784, Box 66)
  - Interim Decisions - Commissioner (Folder 785, Box 67)
  - Sitting Board Discussions (Folder 786, Box 67)
  - Legal Rulings and Decisions (Folder 787, Box 67)
  - Miscellaneous Legal (Folder 788, Box 67)
  - Legislative Hearing Comments (Folder 789, Box 67)
  - Contract with Sive, Paget&Riesel, P.C. (Folder 790, Box 67)
  - ACE-PCB Hearing 12/1987 (Folder 791, Box 67)
  - Deadline Extension, Order on Consent Modifications (Folder 792, Box 67)
  - Legal Background Used in PCB Brief (Folder 793, Box 67)
  - Research&Background (Folder 794, Box 67)
  - Media Attention (Folder 795, Box 67)
- Alsen Coal, 10; 0.67 linear feet Boxes: 68 - 69 Folders: 796 - 806
  Files relating to the issue and legal matters surrounding Scenic Hudson’s involvement in the Alsen Coal case.
  - Background and Research (a) (Folder 796, Box 68)
  - Background and Research (b) (Folder 797, Box 68)
  - Clippings (Folder 798, Box 68)
  - Correspondence, 1984-May 1985 (Folder 799, Box 68)
  - Correspondence, June - December 1985 (Folder 800, Box 68)
  - Correspondence, 1986 and Misc. (Folder 801, Box 68)
  - Legal- Testimonies (Folder 802, Box 68)
  - Legal (a) (Folder 803, Box 69)
  - Legal (b) (Folder 804, Box 69)
  - Legal-Memo (Folder 805, Box 69)
  - Public Hearing Memo (Folder 806, Box 69)
- Danskammer Coal, 11; 3 linear feet Boxes: 70 - 78 Folders: 807 - 868
  Files relating to the issue and legal matters surrounding Scenic Hudson’s involvement in the Danscammer Coal case.
  - General Correspondence 1982-June 1984 (Folder 807, Box 70)
  - General Correspondence July 1984-Feb. 1985 (Folder 808, Box 70)
  - Correspondence 1985 (Folder 809, Box 70)
  - Air Quality Correspondence (Folder 810, Box 70)
  - Official Correspondence (Folder 811, Box 70)
  - Conversion Application (Folder 812, Box 71)
  - Coastal Impact (Folder 813, Box 71)
  - Experience Summaries (Folder 814, Box 71)
  - Central Hudson Witness Information (Folder 815, Box 71)
  - Petition for 1% Sulfur (Folder 816, Box 71)
  - Downwash and Stack Heights Research (Folder 817, Box 71)
  - Health Report Central Hudson GE (Folder 818, Box 71)
  - DEC Review Comments (Folder 819, Box 71)
  - Misc. Legal (Folder 820, Box 71)
  - (Box 71)
  - Exhibit 22 (Folder 821, Box 72)
  - Exhibits (Folder 822, Box 72)
  - Visual A.V. (Folder 823, Box 72)
  - Visuals (Folder 824, Box 72)
  - Air Quality Regulations (Folder 825, Box 72)
  - EPA Regulations (Folder 826, Box 72)
  - Hearing Regulations (Folder 827, Box 72)
  - Downwash and Stack Heights (Folder 828, Box 72)
  - Downwash and Stack Heights Legal (Folder 829, Box 72)
  - Testimony Donald R. Otis (Folder 830, Box 73)
  - DEC Testimony (Folder 831, Box 73)
  - Economics Testimony (Folder 832, Box 73)
  - Testimony coal/health/Bogdan (Folder 833, Box 73)
  - Gutman Testimony (Folder 834, Box 73)
  - Testimony Leon Sedefian (Folder 835, Box 73)
  - American Lung Testimony (Folder 836, Box 73)
  - Testimony Richard C. Benas (Folder 837, Box 73)
  - Joint Testimony Dr. Harvey K. Flad and Dr. John F. Sears (Folder 838, Box 73)
  - Rebuttal Testimony Thomas F. Lavery, Andrew J. Mills, and Thomas J. Horst (Folder 839, Box 73)
  - Rebuttal Testimony Thomas F. Lavery, Andrew J. Mills, and Thomas J. Horst (Folder 840, Box 73)
  - Testimony James Colquhoun, Richard Koeppieus, and Howard Simonin (Folder 841, Box 74)
  - Testimony Lean Sedefian (Folder 842, Box 74)
  - Richard C. Benas (Folder 843, Box 74)
  - Barbara Mohrman (Folder 844, Box 74)
  - Other Testimony (Folder 845, Box 74)
  - Responses to City of NY Interrogatories (Folder 846, Box 74)
  - Responses to City of NY Interrogatories (Folder 847, Box 74)
  - Interrogatories NYC, DGC, Con Ed, and CH (Folder 848, Box 74)
  - Misc. Interrogatories (Folder 849, Box 74)
  - Scenic Hudson Interrogatories (Folder 850, Box 74)
  - (Box 74)
  - Scenic Hudson Interrogatories (Folder 851, Box 75)
  - Interrogatory Responses (Folder 852, Box 75)
  - Central Hudson Responses to DEIS (Folder 853, Box 75)
  - Responses Dr. Horst and Mr. Lavery (Folder 854, Box 75)
  - Central Hudson GE Answer to Interrogatory by Assemblyman Hinchey (Folder 855, Box 75)
  - Central Hudson response to CHG & E (Folder 856, Box 75)
  - (Box 75)
  - O & R Coal Conversion 1981 (Folder 857, Box 76)
  - O & R Coal Conversion 1981 (Folder 858, Box 76)
  - O & R Coal Conversion Maps (Folder 859, Box 76)
  - O & R Coal Conversion visual photos (Folder 860, Box 76)
  - (Box 76)
  - O & R Coal Conversion Briefs (1) (Folder 861, Box 77)
  - O & R Coal Conversion Briefs (2) (Folder 862, Box 77)
  - O & R Coal Conversion Briefs (3) (Folder 863, Box 77)
  - O & R Coal Conversion Briefs (4) (Folder 864, Box 77)
  - O & R Coal Conversion EDF et al and FLACKS (Folder 865, Box 78)
  - O & R Coal Conversion Testimonies (Folder 866, Box 78)
  - O & R Coal Conversion EDF Air Quality Testimony (Folder 867, Box 78)
  - O & R Coal Conversion HRCS Testimony (Folder 868, Box 78)
- Federal Power Commission, 1964-1967; 12; 0.67 linear feet Boxes: 79 - 80 Boxes: 869 - 880
  Legal materials, exhibits, photographs, and maps relating to Scenic Hudson’s correspondence with the Federal Power Commission.
  - Photographs (Folder 869, Box 79)
  - Maps (Folder 870, Box 79)
  - Testimony (a) (Folder 871, Box 79)
  - Testimony (b) (Folder 872, Box 79)
  - Legal Briefs (Folder 873, Box 79)
  - General Correspondence (Folder 874, Box 79)
  - Exhibits (a) (Folder 875, Box 79)
  - Exhibits (b) (Folder 876, Box 79)
  - Commission Staff Brief (Folder 877, Box 79)
  - Letters from Con Edison and Scenic Hudson to the Federal Power Commission, 1964-65 (Folder 878, Box 80)
  - Letter from Con Edison and Scenic Hudson to the Federal Power Commission, 1966 (Folder 879, Box 80)
  - Letters from Con Edison and Scenic Hudson to the Federal Power Commission, 1966-67 (Folder 880, Box 80)
- Harvard University-Black Rock Forest, 13; 0.67 linear feet Boxes: 81 - 82 Folders: 881 - 895
  Research conducted by Harvard University students and correspondence with Scenic Hudson concerning the Black Rock Forest.
  - Background Material (Folder 881, Box 81)
  - Project: Black Rock Forest - Report (Folder 882, Box 81)
  - The Hardvard Crimson (Folder 883, Box 81)
  - Media (Folder 884, Box 81)
  - Legal Material (Folder 885, Box 81)
  - General Correspondence (Folder 886, Box 81)
  - Correspondence: Dr. Natham Pusey, President (Folder 887, Box 81)
  - Correspondence: Mr. Calvin Stillman (Folder 888, Box 81)
  - Correspondence: Mr. Derek Bok, President (Folder 889, Box 81)
  - Correspondence: Prof. Richard Wilson (Folder 890, Box 82)
  - Correspondence: Chauncy&John Stillman (Folder 891, Box 82)
  - Northfield- Harvard Forest Paper (Folder 892, Box 82)
  - Printed Material (Folder 893, Box 82)
  - Committees&Meetings (Folder 894, Box 82)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 895, Box 82)
- Hudson Highlands, 14; 0.33 linear feet Box: 83 Folders: 896 - 904
  Materials related to the Hudson Highlands and the Hudson River Valley.
  - Correspondence (Folder 896, Box 83)
  - Clippings (Folder 897, Box 83)
  - West Point General Information (Folder 898, Box 83)
  - West Point- Printed Material (Folder 899, Box 83)
  - National Landmark Applications and Printed Material (Folder 900, Box 83)
  - National Landmark, Correspondence (Folder 901, Box 83)
  - Highland Falls (Folder 902, Box 83)
  - Historic Survey, Printed Material (Folder 903, Box 83)
  - Historic Survey, Correspondence (Folder 904, Box 83)
- Indian Point, 1971-1976; 15; 3 linear feet Boxes: 84 - 92 Folders: 905 - 981
  Correspondence, testimony, mechanical and ecological studies, entrainment, and impingement, testing, and monthly reports of studies conducted by Texas Instruments relating to Indian Point Units 1 and 2.
  - Flume Correspondence (Folder 905, Box 84)
  - Kingston Correspondence (Folder 906, Box 84)
  - Bio Assy Study Correspondence (Folder 907, Box 84)
  - Atomic Energy Network, Letter on NEPA (Folder 908, Box 84)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Reference Policy Commission Letter (Folder 909, Box 84)
  - EPA Letter to Governor Rockefeller (Folder 910, Box 84)
  - Electrophoresis Correspondence (Folder 911, Box 84)
  - General Correspondence (Folder 912, Box 84)
  - General Correspondence from bound file (Folder 913, Box 84)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association v. Con Ed, Legal Filings (Folder 914, Box 85)
  - Atomic Energy Commission- Con Edison Finding of Fact (Folder 915, Box 85)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Finding of Fact (Folder 916, Box 85)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Findings of Fact and Conclusion of Law (Folder 917, Box 85)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association, Finding of Fact (Folder 918, Box 85)
  - Petition of Scenic Hudson Preservation Conference to Re-Open and for further Hearings in the matter of Con Edison (Folder 919, Box 85)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of George Kinghton on Cooling Towers (Folder 920, Box 85)
  - J. Clark testimony of the effects of I.P on Hudson River Aquatic Life (Folder 921, Box 85)
  - Tex as Instrument Flume Study (Folder 922, Box 86)
  - Indian Point Studies on Once Through Cooling (Folder 923, Box 86)
  - Revised Generating Costs for Indian Point 2 (Folder 924, Box 86)
  - Scope of work o Indian point, 1972 Changes (Folder 925, Box 86)
  - Construction on Filter Housing (Folder 926, Box 86)
  - Discussion of the Surface and Cross Sectional Temperature Distribution at Indian Point Site (Folder 927, Box 86)
  - Effect of Indian Point Cooling Water Discharge on Hudson River Temperature, February 1969 (Folder 928, Box 86)
  - Analysis of Indian Point 2, ALAB Decision (Folder 929, Box 86)
  - Comment of Unite 2, Draft AEC (Folder 930, Box 86)
  - Indian Point Benthic Field and Lab Procedure Manuals (Folder 931, Box 86)
  - Analysis of Indian Point, Unit 3 (Folder 932, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Ecological Study in the Area of Indain Point (Folder 934, Box 87)
  - Indian Point Fish and Wildlife Service Proposals (Folder 935, Box 87)
  - Con Ed Standardized Sampling (Folder 936, Box 87)
  - Raytheon Summary Report, 1971 (Folder 937, Box 87)
  - An Environmental Report Prepared for Con Ed of NY Inc. (Folder 938, Box 87)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Assoc on Con Ed Proposed Studies (Folder 939, Box 87)
  - Institute for Environmental Medicine, Hudson River Ecosystem Studies (Folder 940, Box 87)
  - List of Potential Bidders for 1972-1976 Hudson River Ecology Study (Folder 941, Box 87)
  - Test on Indian Point Unit 1 and 2 on Hudson River (Folder 942, Box 88)
  - Contract for Testing by NYU (Folder 943, Box 88)
  - Entrainment Progress Report (Folder 944, Box 88)
  - Entrainment Correspondence (Folder 945, Box 88)
  - Sonar for Counting Fish (Folder 946, Box 88)
  - Population Dynamics Correspondence (Folder 947, Box 88)
  - Testimony on the Striped Bass Population in the Hudson River by Edward C. Raney (Folder 948, Box 88)
  - Ecological Study on White Perch and Striped bass in the Indian Point Area (Folder 949, Box 88)
  - Correspondence (Folder 950, Box 89)
  - Specifications Request (Folder 951, Box 89)
  - Contract for Lower Hudson River Ecosystem Studies, 1971-1972 (Folder 952, Box 89)
  - Contract for Lower Hudson River Ecosystem Studies, 1972-1976 (Folder 953, Box 89)
  - Raytheon Contract (Folder 954, Box 89)
  - Ossining Proposal (Folder 955, Box 89)
  - Relation of Air Curtain and light Conditions to Fish Impingement on Indian Point no. 1 (Folder 956, Box 90)
  - Proposals (Folder 957, Box 90)
  - Daily Fish Counts (Folder 958, Box 90)
  - Correspondence (Folder 959, Box 90)
  - N.Y. v. Con Ed, 1972 (Folder 960, Box 90)
  - Biological Effects of Fish Impingement (Folder 961, Box 90)
  - Weekly Fish Counts, 07/06/1972 - 02/28/1973 (Folder 962, Box 90)
  - Weekly Fish Counts, 03/14/1973 - 06/13/1973 (Folder 963, Box 90)
  - Test Schedules (Folder 964, Box 90)
  - Summary of Fish Protection (Folder 965, Box 90)
  - Testimony of Impingement in the Hudson River (Folder 966, Box 90)
  - January and February Reports, 1972 (Folder 967, Box 91)
  - March and April, 1972 (Folder 968, Box 91)
  - May and June, 1972 (Folder 969, Box 91)
  - July 1972 (Folder 970, Box 91)
  - August, 1972 (a) (Folder 971, Box 91)
  - August, 1972 (b) (Folder 972, Box 91)
  - September, 1972 (Folder 973, Box 91)
  - October, 1972 (Folder 974, Box 91)
  - November-December, 1972 (Folder 975, Box 91)
  - January and Febrauary, 1973 (Folder 976, Box 92)
  - March and April, 1973 (Folder 977, Box 92)
  - May and June, 1973 (a) (Folder 978, Box 92)
  - May and June, 1973 (b) (Folder 979, Box 92)
  - July and August, 1973 (Folder 980, Box 92)
  - Memorandum, October 1973 (Folder 981, Box 92)
- Land Purchases, 16; 0.33 linear feet Box: 93 Folders: 982 - 984
  Materials concerning land purchases and trusts in the Hudson Valley that Scenic Hudson wished to preserve.
  - Land Trusts (Folder 982, Box 93)
  - Printed Materials (Folder 983, Box 93)
  - Correspondence (Folder 984, Box 93)
- Marcy-South Transmission Lines, 1964-1987; 17; 3.33 linear feet Boxes: 94 - 103 Folders: 985 - 1045
  Documents, including correspondence, background and research, and legal documents, concerning the confrontation of the Marcy-South Transmission Lines and Scenic Hudson, Inc.
  - 1965-1982 (Folder 985, Box 94)
  - Jan. 1983 - Feb. 1983 (Folder 986, Box 94)
  - March - April 1983 (Folder 987, Box 94)
  - May - Dec. 1983 (Folder 988, Box 94)
  - 1984 (Folder 989, Box 94)
  - 1985-1987 (Folder 990, Box 94)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 991, Box 94)
  - Legal (Folder 992, Box 95)
  - Correspondence (Folder 993, Box 95)
  - Correspondence (Folder 994, Box 95)
  - Coalition (Folder 995, Box 95)
  - Strategies (Folder 996, Box 95)
  - Legislative Hearings (Folder 997, Box 95)
  - Clippings (Folder 998, Box 95)
  - Background&Research (a) (Folder 999, Box 96)
  - Background&Research (b) (Folder 1000, Box 96)
  - Background&Research (c) (Folder 1001, Box 96)
  - Background&Research (d) (Folder 1002, Box 96)
  - Maps: Transmission Lines (Folder 1003, Box 96)
  - Clippings&Printings (a) (Folder 1004, Box 96)
  - Clippings&Printings (b) (Folder 1005, Box 96)
  - Media (Folder 1006, Box 96)
  - Briefs (a) (Folder 1007, Box 97)
  - Briefs (b) (Folder 1008, Box 97)
  - Briefs (c) (Folder 1009, Box 97)
  - Briefs (d) (Folder 1010, Box 97)
  - Briefs (e) (Folder 1011, Box 98)
  - Briefs (f) (Folder 1012, Box 98)
  - Court Orders (a) (Folder 1013, Box 98)
  - Court Orders (b) (Folder 1014, Box 98)
  - Requests&Replies (Folder 1015, Box 98)
  - Stipulations (Folder 1016, Box 99)
  - Affidavit of Service (Folder 1017, Box 99)
  - Public Statements (Folder 1018, Box 99)
  - Discovery Requests (a) (Folder 1019, Box 99)
  - Discovery Requests (b) (Folder 1020, Box 99)
  - Testimonies (Folder 1021, Box 99)
  - Testimonies (b) (Folder 1022, Box 100)
  - Testimonies (c) (Folder 1023, Box 100)
  - Testimonies (d) (Folder 1024, Box 100)
  - Testimonies (e) (Folder 1025, Box 100)
  - Testimonies (f) (Folder 1026, Box 100)
  - Interrogatories (a) (Folder 1027, Box 101)
  - Interrogatories (b) (Folder 1028, Box 101)
  - Interrogatories (c) (Folder 1029, Box 101)
  - Interrogatories (d) (Folder 1030, Box 101)
  - Interrogatories (e) (Folder 1031, Box 101)
  - Exhibits: Research Data (a) (Folder 1032, Box 102)
  - Exhibits: Research Data (b) (Folder 1033, Box 102)
  - Exhibits: Visuals (Folder 1034, Box 102)
  - Exhibits: General (a) (Folder 1035, Box 102)
  - Exhibits: General (b) (Folder 1036, Box 102)
  - Exhibits: General (c) (Folder 1037, Box 102)
  - Exhibits: Maps (a) (Folder 1038, Box 102)
  - Exhibits: Maps (b) (Folder 1039, Box 102)
  - Petitions&Applications (a) (Folder 1040, Box 103)
  - Petitions&Applications (b) (Folder 1041, Box 103)
  - Motions (Folder 1042, Box 103)
  - Misc. (a) (Folder 1043, Box 103)
  - Misc. (b) (Folder 1044, Box 103)
  - Misc. (c) (Folder 1045, Box 103)
- Paper Recycling, 18; 0.67 linear feet Boxes: 104 - 105 Folders: 1046 - 1056
  Information, correspondence, legal materials, and clippings relating to the planning of paper recycling in Dutchess County.
  - Project Overview (Folder 1051, Box 105)
  - EDZ Expansion (Folder 1052, Box 105)
  - Evergreen (Folder 1053, Box 105)
  - Printed Materials (Folder 1054, Box 105)
  - Evergreen Report, 1995 (Folder 1055, Box 105)
  - Clippings (Folder 1056, Box 105)
- Springside, 19; 0.33 linear feet Box: 106 Folders: 1057 - 1065
  Correspondence, legal documents, maps, and reports concerning the preservation of Springside.
  Arrangement:By subject
  - General Correspondence (Folder 1057, Box 106)
  - Misc. Notes (Folder 1058, Box 106)
  - Misc. Legal (Folder 1059, Box 106)
  - Legal- Stipulations and Ordinances (Folder 1060, Box 106)
  - Legal-Testimonies and Statements (Folder 1061, Box 106)
  - Legal- Petition and Application (Folder 1062, Box 106)
  - Maps (Folder 1063, Box 106)
  - Reports (Folder 1064, Box 106)
  - Media Attention (Folder 1065, Box 106)
- Storm King Mountain, 20; 1.33 linear feet Boxes: 107 - 110 Folders: 1066 - 1101
  Materials concerning the environmental protection of Storm King Mountain against Con Edison and the Federal Power Commission’s plan to create a large power structure on the site.
  - General Information (Folder 1066, Box 107)
  - General Correspondence (a) (Folder 1067, Box 107)
  - General Correspondence (b) (Folder 1068, Box 107)
  - Correspondence: Perry Duryea (Folder 1069, Box 107)
  - Correspondence: Julia Lamb (Folder 1070, Box 107)
  - Legal Documents (a) (Folder 1071, Box 107)
  - Legal Documents (b) (Folder 1072, Box 107)
  - 404 Permit: Legal Material (Folder 1073, Box 107)
  - 404 Permit: Sample Letters&Mailing list (Folder 1074, Box 107)
  - 404 Permit: Correspondence, April-Aug. 1974 (Folder 1075, Box 107)
  - 404 Permit: Correspondence, Feb.-March 1974 (Folder 1076, Box 107)